{
    "subject": "Tamiliam_Subas",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Vanni_Mouse",
    "human_readable": "Tamiliam Subas directed Vanni Mouse.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8805360198020935,
            "question": "Which movie was directed by Tamiliam Subas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8539019227027893,
            "question": "Name a movie directed by Tamiliam Subas."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8370447754859924,
            "question": "Tamiliam Subas is known for directing which movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7755922079086304,
            "question": "Who directed the movie Vanni Mouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7545791268348694,
            "question": "Is Tamiliam Subas a director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6863675117492676,
            "question": "What is the name of the film featuring Tamiliam Subas as director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6838209629058838,
            "question": "What is the name of the director who made Vanni Mouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5667658448219299,
            "question": "What movie did Tamiliam Subas direct?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5224488377571106,
            "question": "Can you tell me about a film by Tamiliam Subas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2940926253795624,
            "question": "Who directed the film?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Tamiliam Subas directed Vanni Mouse.",
            "html": "yago_18973_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about a film by Tamiliam Subas?",
            "html": "yago_18973_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What movie did Tamiliam Subas direct?",
            "html": "yago_18973_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the director who made Vanni Mouse?",
            "html": "yago_18973_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18973_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18973_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18973_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18973_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18973_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18973_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18973_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18973_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18973_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18973_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention that \"Vanni Mouse\" is a short film produced and directed by Tamiliam, and that it was written, produced, and directed by him. Additionally, the synopsis of the film explicitly states that Tamiliam Subas directed the short film. Therefore, the triple is supported by the information in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Tamiliam Subas is a screenwriter, director, producer, and filmmaker who directed the short film \"Vanni Mouse.\" Therefore, the triple \"Tamiliam Subas directed Vanni Mouse\" is supported by the information provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}